- [In Unison] Soulja
Boy off in this ho
Watch me crank
that, watch me roll
Watch me crank that
Soulja Boy and Superman!
And watch me yuuuuuuu!
- Who is Soulja Boy? And what
in the heck is that dance?
- Who's Soulja Boy?!
♪ Yuuuuuuu ♪
♪ Soulja Boy tell 'em ♪
♪ Ayy, I got this new dance for
y'all called the Soulja Boy ♪
♪ You just gotta punch then
crank back three times ♪
♪ From left to right ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank that Soulja
Boy then Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank dat Soulja
Boy then Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch
Soulja Boy up in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me lean
then watch me rock ♪
♪ Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Yeah, watch me
crank that Robocop ♪
♪ Super fresh, now
watch me jock ♪
♪ Jocking on them haters, man ♪
♪ When I do that Soulja Boy ♪
♪ I lean to the left then crank
that thang, now (yuuuuuu) ♪
♪ I'm jocking on yo'
(I'm jocking on yo') ♪
♪ And if we get to fightin'
then I'm on yo' ♪
♪ I'm on yo' ♪
♪ You catch me at yo'
local party, yes, I
crank it everyday ♪
♪ Haters gettin' mad 'cause ♪
♪ "I got me some Bathing Ape" ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank dat Soulja
Boy then Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank dat Soulja
boy then Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch
I'm bouncin' on my toes ♪
♪ Watch me super soak that ho ♪
♪ I'ma pass it to Arab and he
gon' crank it up fo' sho' ♪
♪ Haters wanna be me,
Soulja Boy, I'm the man ♪
♪ They be lookin' at my neck,
sayin' it's the rubber band ♪
♪ Man (man), watch me
do it (watch me do it) ♪
♪ Dance (dance), let's get
to it (let's get to it) ♪
♪ Nope, you can't do
it like me, though ♪
♪ So don't do it like me, folk ♪
♪ I see you tryna
do it like me, man
that damn ugly ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank that Soulja
Boy then Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank dat Soulja
Boy then Superman that ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch
I'm too fresh,
off in that ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank that Roosevelt,
then super soak that ho ♪
♪ Super soak that ho ♪
♪ I'm too fresh, now
watch me (do it) ♪
♪ Watch me shuffle,
watch me (yuuuuuuu) ♪
♪ Watch me crank
that Soulja Boy ♪
♪ Now Superman, yuuuuuuu ♪
♪ Superman, do it ♪
♪ Ahhh ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank dat Soulja
Boy then Superman that ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch ♪
♪ Soulja Boy off in this ho ♪
♪ Watch me crank
it, watch me roll ♪
♪ Watch me crank dat Soulja
Boy then Superman dat ho ♪
♪ Now watch me yuuuuuuu
(Crank dat Soulja Boy) ♪
♪ Now watch ♪
(instrumental)
♪ Yuuuuuuu ♪
♪ Ahhh ♪
♪ Yuuuuuuu! ♪